Inventory of the Germany (Territory Under Allied Occupation, 1945-1955) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Allied Control Authority Coordinating Committee (ACAC), 1945-1949 (Box 1-55)
  - Bipartite organization (Bizone), 1946-1949 (Folder 41-54)
    - Control Office (BICO), 1946-1949 (Folder 44-50)
      - Secretariat papers, (contd.), 1947-1949 (Folder 48:1-13)
      - Secretariat papers, (contd.), 1947-1949 (Folder 49:1)
      - Agenda, 1947-1948 (Folder 49:2)
      - Minutes, 1947-1948 (Folder 49:3-7)
      - Memoranda, 1947-1949 (Folder 49:8)
      - Joint Secretariat, 1947-1949 (Folder 49:9-13)
      - Legal Gazette of the Combined Economic Area, (GL), 1948-1949 (Folder 49:14-15)
      - Legal Gazette (GL), (contd.), 1948-1949 (Folder 50:1-2)
      - European Recovery Program (ERP), 1948-1949 (Folder 50:3-7)
    - Civil Service Committee (BICIV), 1946-1947 (Folder 50:8)
    - Communication Panel (BICOM), 1946-1947 (Folder 50-51)
      - Agenda, 1947 (Folder 50:9)
      - Minutes, 1947 (Folder 50:10)
      - Memoranda, 1947 (Folder 50:11)
      - Secretariat papers, 1946-1947 (Folder 50:12-13)
      - Miscellany, 1947 (Folder 50:14)
      - Miscellany (contd.), 1947 (Folder 51:1)
    - Economic Panel (BIECO), 1947 (Folder 51-52)
      - Agenda, 1947 (Folder 51:2)
      - Minutes, 1947 (Folder 51:3-8)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947 (Folder 51:9-15)
      - Secretariat papers, (contd.), 1947 (Folder 52:1-7)
      - Railway Supplies Committee (RAIL), 1947 (Folder 52:8)
    - Food and Administration Panel (BIF&A), 1947 (Folder 52)
      - Agenda, 1947 (Folder 52:9)
      - Minutes, 1947 (Folder 52:10)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947 (Folder 52:11-13)
    - Finance Panel (BIFIN), 1947 (Folder 52-53)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947 (Folder 52:14-15)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947 (Folder 53:1-2)
      - Miscellany, 1947 (Folder 53:3)
    - Secretariat (BISEC), memoranda, 1947-1949 (Folder 53:4-10)
    - Transport Panel (BITRT), 1947 (Folder 53-54)
      - Agenda, 1947 (Folder 53:11)
      - Minutes, 1947 (Folder 53:12)
      - Memoranda, 1947 (Folder 53:13)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947 (Folder 53:14-15)
      - Secretariat papers, (contd.), 1947 (Folder 54:1-2)
    - Financial Adviser (BFA), 1947-1948 (Folder 54)
      - Minutes, 1947 (Folder 54:3)
      - Secretariat papers, 1947-1948 (Folder 54:4)
    - Civil Aviation Panel (BIAIR), 1947 (Folder 54:5-6)
    - Information Bulletin, 1946-1947 (Folder 54:7)
    - Press releases, 1948 (Folder 54:8-9)
    - Combined Area Monthly Progress Report, by Deutsche Kohlenbergbau (Statistics Department) for UK/US Coal Control Group, 1949 (Folder 54:10)
    - Miscellany, 1947 (Folder 54:11)
  - Three Western Zones (Trizone) (TRIB), 1945-1949 (Folder 54-55)
    - Agenda, 1948 (Folder 54:12)
    - Minutes, 1949 (Folder 54:13)
    - Secretariat papers, 1949 (Folder 54:14-15)
    - Secretariat papers, (contd.), 1949 (Folder 55:1)
    - Joint Export-Import Agency (JEIM), 1948-1949 (Folder 55)
      - Secretariat papers, 1949 (Folder 55:2)
      - Board of Directors (JEIB), 1947 (Folder 55:3)
      - Foreign Trade Division, 1947 (Folder 55:4)
    - Meetings of the Military Governors and Ministers-President of the Western Zones (MGMP) on Future German Political Organization, minutes, 1948-1949 (Folder 55:5)
    - Combined Nutrition Committee (US/BR/FR), report, 1945 (Folder 55:6)
  - Control Commission for Germany (British Element), 1947-1949 (Folder 55)
    - Press Releases, 1947-1949 (Folder 55)
      - Public Relation Branch, 1947-1949 (Folder 55:7-8)
      - Press Branch, 1947-1948 (Folder 55:9-12)
      - Information Center, 1949 (Folder 55:13-14)
    - Military Government Gazette, Germany, British Zone of Control, 1949 (Folder 55:15)